Claire said she wanted to go back to work.
Are you crazy?
You want me to go back to work?
Someone leaked that Claire hired
Yo and Patchy to be her friends.
Socialite Claire's back in the news?
Ms. Claire's really here!
Ms. Claire, can we get a statement?
I'm here to demand justice for my friend.
My friend is dead,
and yet nobody is saying a word about it.
I'm worried about one thing.
She won't tell her the truth, right?
Are you doing okay?
I mean,
my people didn't hurt you, right?
Ms. Claire,
if you have something to say to me,
just say it.
Don't beat around the bush.
If you don't mind,
could you tell me
what happened
after the helicopter crash that day?
And why do you want to know?
Well, you want me to take responsibility.
I was unconscious for months.
If I had known sooner,
I would've tried to get in touch
and take responsibility, like you wanted.
Do you really want to know,
or... are you just playing a part?
I really want to know.
Before the crash,
Ms. Jinla told me
if she died, nobody would care.
What?
Jin told you that?
How could she not know
how devastated I would be?
Jin, how did the interview
with Ms. Khaedarun go?
Are you done? Tell me all about it.
It's been hours.
Why haven't you replied, Jin?
We have some breaking news.
A helicopter carrying
Ms. Khaedarun Kanchathara,
an executive of TGL Group,
has crashed in the Nakhon Nayok area.
We understand there are
two confirmed fatalities:
the pilot and a member
of Ms. Khaedarun's team
who flew out with her for an interview.
We will bring you more updates
as soon as they become available.
Despite the news report,
I refused to believe my friend was gone.
She died, and you're not
gonna take responsibility?
Because I wanted to believe
a miracle would happen for her.
But in the end,
- miracles aren't real.
- Jin.
I'm so sorry.
But you know what was real?
Your inhumanity.
None of you has even bothered
to offer her an apology.
My friend Jinla was a good person.
And I never thought...
we'd be torn apart so soon.
I...
I sympathize and...
I'm sorry you lost your best friend.
But you know it was an accident, right?
And since it was an accident,
you have no right to demand anything.
So what?
Are you calling the cops to arrest me?
Go ahead. Call them right now.
No.
I know you're doing this
because you feel guilty about Ms. Jinla.
Why would I feel guilty about her?
Because it was you...
who should've been on that chopper.
You were supposed to interview me,
but you made Ms. Jinla go instead.
If you want to repay me,
I have a job for you.
What job?
Socialite Claire.
Khaedarun Kanchathara.
How did you know about that?
Ms. Jinla told me that day.
Do you have any more questions?
If not,
I'll take my leave.
Ms. Wan.
Thank you.
For what?
Nothing.
I just feel like if I were Ms. Jinla,
I would want to thank you
for loving her so much.
And please...
don't feel guilty.
It was an accident.
Stop blaming yourself.
Are you okay?
What were you two talking about?
Why did she...?
She's not mad at Ms. Claire.
She's mad at herself.
Actually,
the one who was supposed
to be on that chopper was...
Wan.
But she made me go instead.
So she thinks I died because of her.
Ms. Wan really cares about you.
I didn't get a chance to tell you
that I met Ms. Wan at your house,
She was being harassed by your creditors.
Did... did they do anything to her?
Not yet.
They wanted her to pay off your debt.
No, they can't do that.
I need to talk to them.
There's no need.
I already taught them a lesson.
But what I'm trying to tell you is,
even though she thinks you're dead,
she's still doing her best
to protect that house for you.
Hey,
I'm begging you.
Please let it go this time.
I don't want her to get a criminal record.
- Please...
- Don't say another word.
Tun.
Do what you need to do
to get the best outcome.
Okay.
Hey.
I need one more favor.
My scrapbook is in the car, right?
You can't.
I haven't even said anything.
You don't have to. I know what you want.
You want to...
You want to visit your aunt,
so you're using the scrapbook
as an excuse.
I didn't even say I wanted to.
I know my duty.
I know what I have to do today.
I was gonna ask you to go in my place.
But today is your first day back.
I don't want to leave you by yourself.
I get that.
But my aunt can't wait.
Right now, every second counts for her.
Please take that scrapbook to her for me.
Maybe...
she'll remember something and feel better.
Come on, I'll show you that
I can pull off
your elegant and fabulous demeanor.
Mr. Chris?
- Did you need something?
- Oh, I figured
it was your first day back at work,
so I wanted to congratulate you.
I see.
I wouldn't call it
my first day back at work.
It's more like therapy.
Grandpa and Chan wanted me here,
hoping it might help get my memory back.
Right.
I totally forgot you have amnesia.
But just seeing you back
makes me really happy.
Uh, Mr. Chan gave me
some documents to look over.
If there's nothing else,
I need to get back to work.
Ms. Claire,
do you remember your own secret?
My secret?
Yes.
The secret that only you and I know.
What did you say?
Our PR team told you to take down
the video from your website?
You're a fraud!
Ms. Rose,
even if you take it down,
people can still share it.
Well, that's for you to decide.
That woman?
She's probably a friend of the woman
who died in the crash.
But how you want to spin the story
is entirely up to you.
I have only one request.
My company and I must not be involved.
Chris.
CHA
Where is he?
Why did he leave the phone here?
Chris?
Get me the facilities department
I want to check the security footage.
Where are we going?
To a place that will bring
your memory back.
Please.
I have to apologize.
I took the liberty of
grabbing your access card.
After you.
This is a restricted floor,
accessible only to C-level executives.
What's on this floor?
It sounds so mysterious.
It's where the company keeps
its confidential documents.
Especially this room.
What room is it?
Do you really not remember this room?
It's where you keep all the company's
architectural drawings.
You mean like the ones
for housing and condo projects?
Are they that confidential?
What's so funny?
The first time you brought me up here,
I asked you the same question.
And you told me
these documents have to be kept
under extra-tight security
because if they leaked, our competitors
might copy them and beat us to market.
Are you starting to remember anything?
No.
It's gonna take some time.
Thank you for bringing me up here.
Let's head back down.
I need to get back to work.
Hold on, Ms. Claire.
Do you really not remember
what we were doing up here?
TWO YEARS AGO
Why did you bring me up here?
Why do you think I brought you
to a place where we'd be alone?
Someone's here.
I felt like playing
hide-and-seek with Cha.
I wanted to see
if your girlfriend could find us.
I should leave.
Hold on, what's the rush?
Isn't this kind of thrilling?
Ms. Claire,
you know what will happen
if Cha catches us here alone.
Claire!
What will happen?
‎You!
Claire!
Stop!
Claire! Open this door right now!
Open!
Claire!
Will she be able to get in here?
Don't worry.
It's only accessible to me.
Claire!
Open!
See?
Isn't this exciting?
Claire!
Open!
Chris!
Did I really do that?
Yes.
That's the secret about you.
What are you doing?
Bringing your memory back.
Hey, stop it.
Stop doing this to me.
I used to like you
because I thought you were a good guy.
Stay away from me.
I promised Cha I'd stay away from you.
Claire, come on.
But I miss you, Claire.
- Stop.
- Claire.
Hey, get off me!
No!
Get off me! Stop! Hey!
Cha.
She has access to this floor too.
Open the door now.
- What am I supposed to do?
- Look at the camera.
What are you doing?
Cha.
Uh, well...
I needed the Agriv drawings.
You know only Claire can unlock this room.
Yes.
We're here to see
the architectural drawings.
- Let's go.
- Hold on.
Open it then.
I'd love to see them too.
Sure.
I might not have looked
directly at the camera.
Let me try again.
Hey,
you know this security system
is top-of-the-line.
It will lock us out
after three failed attempts.
We'll have to bring in technicians
from overseas to reset it.
I've already contacted them.
You might not have been informed,
but the system
started acting up six months ago.
Since Ms. Claire was
recovering at the time,
I didn't bring them in.
Now that she's doing better,
they've confirmed
they'll be here within this month.
Are you sure it's a system issue?
What do you mean by that?
You saw it yourself. It's a system issue.
Besides,
what you're doing is inappropriate.
You shouldn't be giving Claire orders.
The only person who can
give her orders is the chairman.
If there's nothing else,
it's best you head back downstairs.
Why did you come up here?
I didn't want to.
Mr. Chris brought me here.
He said Ms. Claire brought him up here,
so he showed me.
He thought it'd bring back my memory.
Wait,
you knew Ms. Claire and Mr. Chris
came up here together, didn't you?
Let's head down.
Wait.
How did you know I was up here?
Claire!
KHAEDARUN KANTHARA
VICE PRESIDENT
Hey.
Thank you very much.
Instead of thanking me,
you'd better start listening to me.
Can't you be nice for once?
Honestly, I didn't need to thank you.
Because that scanner was already broken.
The scanner isn't broken.
It's not?
Then why did my attempts fail?
I have Ms. Claire's face.
Because the system...
looks for Claire's iris, not yours.
Then what are you going to do?
We'll talk downstairs.
I know we had our differences.
But let's start over.
Hello, everyone.
Get me the engineer in charge of
the vault's security system.
Chris, do you think the Claire we see
walking around is the real deal?
Why do you ask that?
I brought the technicians who installed
the vault's scanner in to check it.
They said it worked fine.
What does that mean?
Chris, have you ever wondered
if the Claire we see walking around
is the real deal or an imposter?
I still don't get it.
We can see that it's her.
Sure.
She might look like her on the outside,
but who knows what's on the inside?
And isn't it weird?
Ever since Chan brought her back,
Claire's been acting weird.
I mean, yeah, she's been weird,
but she has amnesia.
What if Chan got someone
to impersonate Claire
and claim she has amnesia?
Then how do we find out
if this Claire is real or fake?
- Claire!
- Cha!
- No!
- Cha, no! Cha!
How dare the two of you do this to me?
Cha. Cha, please stop.
- Claire! You!
- Cha!
- Stop it, Cha.
- How does it feel?
Being done this dirty
by the guy you're head over heels for?
Does it hurt?
- I'm gonna kill you!
- Cha!
- Stop, Cha.
- No!
- Cha.
- Let go!
- Get off me!
Why are you so mad?
You should be thanking me instead.
- Stop, Cha.
- Let go!
- Cha! Cha!
- Claire!
Cha! Cha, no! Cha!
If she's the real Claire,
she'll have a scar on her back.
Hold on. Hey.
Do you think Ms. Cha told
the chairman about the vault?
No.
She knows how much he loves Claire.
She wouldn't do anything without proof.
It's too risky.
But I still don't get why Ms. Claire
wanted to beat Ms. Cha so badly
that she would sleep with...
Whatever.
If that was the case,
why didn't she just ask her grandfather
to kick Ms. Cha
and Aunt Rin out of the house?
Why tolerate living under the same roof?
It's because of the will.
The will?
You two told him
to change the will, didn't you?
Claire, listen to me.
Cha and I had no idea
why Mr. Thiwa called Mr. Suthee over.
But we never told Mr. Thiwa
to change the will like you think.
Really?
If that's true,
are you two standing here
to beg him for a handout?
A handout?
Mom,
maybe Dad really did call
the lawyer to change the will.
Because he loves you very much,
and he can't stand seeing anyone hurt her.
When that time comes, who knows
who'll be begging who for a handout.
No way.
He'd never choose you two over me.
If you really believe that,
why are you acting like a scalded dog?
But don't you worry.
If Dad really leaves everything
to the two of us,
when the time comes,
I'll donate some money to
the mental asylum you'll be staying in.
You bitch.
- What?
- Claire! Claire!
- Wanna try me?
- Claire.
- Why not?
- Please stop. Stop, stop.
- Stop.
- Chan, Chan, let go. I said...
- Let go of me.
- What is all this racket?!
Didn't you know we were talking?
Please take care of it, Mr. Suthee.
Yes, sir. I'll take my leave.
Why did you call Mr. Suthee over?
I just wanted to tweak the will.
Tweak the will?
Why?
Did someone make you?
You're not legally married to him,
so you made him change the will.
I told you my mom didn't do it.
Cut the crap.
Anyone can see you two are dying
to get your hands on his fortune.
Claire!
Nobody can make me do anything.
If I were to leave
a part of my estate to Cha,
it wouldn't be all that strange.
Since Aunt Rin is my wife,
Cha's like my own child.
Are you saying...
you're gonna leave them the inheritance?
Everything will only be revealed
after I'm dead.
What does that mean, honey?
I get it now.
Everyone thinks he's going to leave
the inheritance to the other side.
So they tolerate living together.
And both sides
have to do whatever it takes
to make the other side
miserable enough to leave.
Hey.
Then Ms. Cha will never
let the vault thing slide.
Have you thought of a plan?
What?
Hey.
What? Hey. Hey.
Hey, wait.
You didn't answer me.
How was it, Claire?
Your first day on the job.
Uh, it went okay.
Get any memory back?
Not much, sir.
She only recalled one thing,
how to boss me around.
You're still up, Grandpa.
I was staying up
to ask how your first day went.
And I wanted to discuss
some business with Chan.
Let me talk to him for a bit.
Go get some rest.
Come on, Chan.
Yes, sir.
What do you think he wants to talk about?
It's nothing.
It's my job to give him daily updates
on company business.
You had a long day. Go get some rest.
Can you guess what I wanted to talk about?
Is it about Claire hiring
those celebrities to be her friends?
Her hiring those celebs to be her friends?
That's so Claire!
That didn't surprise me at all.
What I actually wanted to talk to you
is about the woman who ambushed Claire.
How could her security be that lax?
What if that woman had a gun?
I apologize, sir.
But I've instructed the security
and facilities departments
to strictly screen everyone coming in.
Of course you have.
And how are you gonna handle that woman?
I already handled it.
Go wait outside. I'll talk to him.
Please don't hurt Ms. Wan.
She was just angry about her friend.
Who said I would hurt her?
I have no intention of hurting her.
Oh, then...
what did you mean when you asked him
how we were going to handle her?
I was referring to the woman named Jinla.
When I saw the news today,
I had my people look into her.
But I just recalled that
the woman named Jinla
was with you in the crash.
Chan, do you know this woman Jinla?
I don't know her personally, sir.
I only know she was the one interviewing
Claire on the day of the crash.
Is there something on your mind?
Poor woman.
She lived with her aunt.
And when she passed away,
her aunt ended up...
Grandpa, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Her aunt must've loved her
just as much as I love you.
And if I were her aunt,
I wouldn't be able to cope either.
If her aunt were still around,
I'd have offered her
some financial relief.
Hey, Chan.
I want you to look after her affairs,
even though she's gone.
Help those around her as best as we can.
Understood.
As for you,
live your life from now on,
knowing its true value.
Because many people don't get
a second chance at life like you did.
I will.
Go get some rest.
That's all I wanted to talk about.
Oh, Chan.
Sir?
I hope you haven't forgotten
the promise you made to me.
I have not.
Aren't you gonna walk me to my room?
You're doing great now.
Walking there alone should be a breeze.
What are you mad at me for?
I see.
You're mad because
I eavesdropped on your conversation.
And the way you popped out like that
and acted all chummy with Ms. Wan,
you don't think he'd find that suspicious?
Well, I was afraid he would order you
to do something to Wan.
Order me to do something to her?
You seriously think
he would order me to hurt her or kill her?
Hey, this is real life, not a drama.
How could we just kill someone, huh?
Really?
What about what you did to me?
It was basically the same as killing me.
You talk back a lot these days.
If you don't want me to,
you should've sewn my mouth shut
when you changed my face.
With your smart mouth,
walk to your room yourself.
Do you think I can't manage?
It's just right there. Whatever.
I hope you haven't forgotten
the promise you made to me.
I, NITCHAN SATHITPHONG, PROMISE THAT
I WILL ONLY MARRY KHAEDARUN KANCHATHARA.
Give me your hand.
I, NITCHAN SATHITPHONG, PROMISE THAT
I WILL ONLY MARRY KHAEDARUN KANCHATHARA.
I came to tell you to do your job.
You haven't checked my room yet.
Aren't you going to check
if anyone snuck in there?
I'll have Tun do that later.
Hey, wait.
What are you hiding in there?
Let me see.
It's nothing.
Go ahead. I'll be right there.
It must be something about me.
Let me look.
There's nothing about you in here.
If that's true,
why won't you let me see it?
- Let me see.
- I said it's nothing.
Are you hiding something again?
You must be hiding something from me.
What are you doing?
- It's nothing.
- I don't know. Let me see.
- Hey.
I want you to wear this bracelet.
You're gonna tell your dad the woman
he sees isn't the real Claire.
You think he'll believe you?
Your only job is to do whatever it takes
to make Dad love and trust you again.
As for Claire, I'll handle her.
There might be someone else
who wants to ruin both of us.
You can see that's Claire.
Whether she's real or fake,
she won't survive tonight.
This is the last time I'll let this slide.
If something like this happens again,
I'll use the power the chairman gave me
to take decisive action.